<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><timedtext format="3">
<body>
<p t="1320" d="7560">﻿Hello peachies, welcome 
back to dear peachie!
 </p>
<p t="8880" d="3900">In our video today, we are going 
to show you a quick tutorial for  </p>
<p t="12780" d="4140">this douyin dolly soft glam look.
This beauty guru here named Xiao Ta,  </p>
<p t="16920" d="4500">and she has gained more than 200 thousands 
followers on her xiao hong shu,
 </p>
<p t="21420" d="3660">If you love to try douyin makeup 
but do not know how to start?
 </p>
<p t="25080" d="2040">This look is perfect for you to begin!
 </p>
<p t="27120" d="5340">First, Ta is going to prep her 
skin before applying her base.
 </p>
<p t="32460" d="4200">She is moisturising the dry patches on 
her face using the serum balm stick,
 </p>
<p t="36660" d="5820">Such as the sides of nose, mouth corners and under 
eye to avoid your base from creasing later. 
 </p>
<p t="42480" d="4680">If you face the same issue, you can 
apply any lightweight moisturiser that  </p>
<p t="47160" d="3900">you have on those dry patches 
Let the moisturiser set for around  </p>
<p t="51060" d="5340">15 minutes before you apply any makeup, so that 
the moisturizer gets absorbed by the skin 
 </p>
<p t="56400" d="3540">Once the skincare is set into 
your skin, layer a thin coat of  </p>
<p t="59940" d="3540">foundation to even out your skin tone.
Pat them out with a cushion sponge.
 </p>
<p t="63480" d="4200">Matte highlighter is dabbed at the inner cheeks 
to brighten the center region of her face. 
 </p>
<p t="67680" d="3180">You can also use a lighter shade 
of concealer to do so.
 </p>
<p t="70860" d="3840">Then, put on some setting powder 
to achieve that natural look.
 </p>
<p t="74700" d="3420">For brows, Ta is filling them 
in with brow powder.
 </p>
<p t="78120" d="5040">She mentions that she prefer the light and 
fuzzy looking brows today, nothing too angular,  </p>
<p t="83160" d="5760">just follow your natural brow shape will do.
Next, she contours her nose from the nose roots  </p>
<p t="88920" d="3060">towards the nose bridge,
And she fills in a V shape at  </p>
<p t="91980" d="3180">her nose tip with a light hand,
Add a little bit of contour at the  </p>
<p t="95160" d="4320">lower lip and philtrum to deepen their shadow, 
it can make your lips look more pouty!
 </p>
<p t="99480" d="4320">If you’re going for a cute look, you do not 
need to apply contour to your jaws, 
 </p>
<p t="103800" d="3000">The chiselled jaw might actually 
make your makeup look sexier,  </p>
<p t="106800" d="4620">instead of making it appear more dolly!
Contour to bring your cheekbones inwards,  </p>
<p t="111420" d="3240">so your face shape will look less 
angular to match with this look.
 </p>
<p t="114660" d="3780">And add a little bit below your chin to make 
your face look shorter and younger. 
 </p>
<p t="118440" d="4860">For eyes and blush, Ta is going to use a 
warm pink shade blusher from a China brand,  </p>
<p t="124080" d="3480">called Girl cult in the shade Fuwa.
She said just a light touch all over your  </p>
<p t="127560" d="3720">lid is enough, emphasise more on 
the lower lid and aygeosahl.
 </p>
<p t="131280" d="4740">For blush, apply the same blush at the same region 
where you apply the matte highlighter. 
 </p>
<p t="136020" d="5160">Apply some at the nose tip and chin. 
Eyelashes is a must to enhance your eye shape,  </p>
<p t="141180" d="3300">besides curling them,
Ta is putting on the individual  </p>
<p t="144480" d="4860">falsies to accentuate her actual lashes. 
Fill in the blank spots at your inner lash line  </p>
<p t="149340" d="2580">with a liquid liner. 
Extend a winged liner from  </p>
<p t="151920" d="2820">your outer corner. 
With an aygeosahl liner,  </p>
<p t="154740" d="4380">Ta is going over to her contour again to deepen 
the shadow at the centre of her pupil. 
 </p>
<p t="159120" d="3300">Add more at the lower lash line to 
make your eyes look rounder.
 </p>
<p t="162420" d="2940">Highlight the center of your 
aygeosahl and inner corner. 
 </p>
<p t="165360" d="2820">Apply a light pink lip shine 
for that glossy lip look.
 </p>
<p t="168180" d="4860">Lastly, she dabs the shimmery highlighter 
at the tip of her nose and nose bridge,  </p>
<p t="173040" d="2760">and inner corner.
And the look is done!
 </p>
<p t="176640" d="4620">A very refreshing, cute and dolly makeup 
look that is perfect for any occasion!
 </p>
<p t="181260" d="2760">We just love how girly and 
adorable she looks here.
 </p>
<p t="184020" d="3300">What do you guys think?
Comment down below to let us know!
 </p>
<p t="187320" d="3720">Thank you so much for watching, we 
will see you in the next video.
 </p>
<p t="191040" d="960">Good bye!</p>
</body>
</timedtext>
